Guide to the Tyree Scott Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- UNITED CONSTRUCTION WORKERS ASSOCIATION RECORDS, 1962-1985; SERIES 1 (Box-folder 1/1-11/33)
  - Organizational Records, 1962-1985; Subseries A (Box-folder 1/1-10/15)
    - Membership Applications, 1965-1985; Part 8 (Box-folder 3/1-3/49)
      - Applicants for Apprenticeship, 1979 (Box-folder 3/42)
      - Applications for Apprenticeships, 1979 (Box-folder 3/43)
      - Membership Applications: Resumes, Prior to 1973 (Box-folder 3/44)
      - Washington State Applications, 1972 (Box-folder 3/45)
      - Cheryl Marlow, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 3/46)
      - Debra Favors, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 3/47)
      - Membership Applications: Y, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 3/48)
      - Court Report: U.S. Attorney Office, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 3/49)
    - Manpower Compliance Reports, 1965-1985; Part 9 (Box-folder 4/1-5/27)
      - University of Washington Reports (Part 1 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 4/1)
      - University of Washington Reports (Part 2 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 4/2)
      - Washington State Highway Contract (Part 1 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 4/3)
      - Washington State Highway Contract (Part 2 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 4/4)
      - Washington State Highway Contract (Part 3 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 4/5)
      - I-90 Highway Reporting Forms, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 4/6)
      - Weyerhaeuser Project, circa 1970s (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Domed Stadium/Weekly Reports #3 (Part 1 of 2), 1976 (Box-folder 4/8)
      - Domed Stadium/Weekly Reports #3 (Part 2 of 2), 1976 (Box-folder 4/9)
      - Domed Stadium Weekly Reports (Part 1 of 2), 1975 (Box-folder 4/10)
      - Domed Stadium Weekly Reports (Part 2 of 2), 1975 (Box-folder 4/11)
      - Highway Reporting Forms (Part 1 of 2), 1976 (Box-folder 4/12)
      - Highway Reporting Forms (Part 2 of 2), 1976 (Box-folder 4/13)
      - Highway Reporting Forms (Part 1 of 2), 1976 (Box-folder 4/14)
      - Highway Reporting Forms (Part 2 of 2), 1976 (Box-folder 4/15)
      - Contract Compliance, July 1974-December 1974 (Box-folder 4/16)
      - Howard S. Wright, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 4/17)
      - Santa Fe Refit Industrial Facility, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 4/18)
      - Rainier Tower Weekly Reports (Part 1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 4/19)
      - Rainier Tower Weekly Reports (Part 2 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 4/20)
      - Daily Work Sheets from Larkin Potts, 1976 (Box-folder 5/1)
      - Trident Venture Construction, 1976 (Box-folder 5/2)
      - Trident Project (H.S. Wright), 1976 (Box-folder 5/3)
      - Washington State Highway I-90, 1976 (Box-folder 5/4)
      - University of Washington, 1976 (Box-folder 5/5)
      - Larkin Potts, 1976 (Box-folder 5/6)
      - Trident Project (Santa Fe), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5/7)
      - Contract Compliance, July 1973-September 1973 (Box-folder 5/8)
      - Contract Compliance Reports, January 1973-March 1973 (Box-folder 5/9)
      - Contract Compliance Reports, July 1972-September 1972 (Box-folder 5/10)
      - Contract Compliance Reports, October 1972-December 1972 (Box-folder 5/11)
      - Contract Compliance Reports, January 1972-March 1972 (Box-folder 5/12)
      - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission Bi-Monthly Reports, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5/13)
      - Washington State Highway I-90, October 1976 (Box-folder 5/14)
      - Court Order Advisory Committee, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 5/15)
      - Highway Department, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 5/16)
      - King-Snohomish Manpower Contracts, 1974 (Box-folder 5/17)
      - Santa Fe Engineers Inc. Job No. 427, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 5/18)
      - Contract Compliance Reports, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 5/19)
      - Contract Compliance Reports, April 1972-June 1972 (Box-folder 5/20)
      - Contract Compliance Reports, January 1974-June 1974 (Box-folder 5/21)
      - Follow-Up Materials, 1971 (Box-folder 5/22)
      - Apprenticeship Program, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 5/23)
      - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission Legal, 1978 (Box-folder 5/24)
      - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission Legal, 1978 (Box-folder 5/25)
      - Contract Compliance, April 1973-June 1973 (Box-folder 5/26)
      - Salaries, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5/27)
    - Reports, 1972-1981; Part 10 (Box-folder 6/1-6/6)
      - Proposals, 1973 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Proposals, 1972 (Box-folder 6/2)
      - Regarding Special Apprentices (U.S. Attorney), 1972 (Box-folder 6/3)
      - Important Letters, Proposals, Documents, Etc, 1976 (Box-folder 6/4)
      - Reports, 1981 (Box-folder 6/5)
      - Court Order, 1972 (Box-folder 6/6)
    - Speeches and Writings, 1965-1985; Part 11 (Box-folder 6/7-6/11)
      - Speeches and Writings, January 1974 (Box-folder 6/7)
      - Speeches and Writings, 1981 (Box-folder 6/8)
      - William Little Dissertation, 1975 (Box-folder 6/9)
      - "The Seattle Building Trades Decree", circa 1970s (Box-folder 6/10)
      - Speeches and Writings, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 6/11)
    - Press Statements and Releases, 1970-1981; Part 12 (Box-folder 6/12-6/18)
      - Public Statement regarding Demonstration on 12/17/70, 1970 (Box-folder 6/12)
      - Statements, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 6/13)
      - Statements, 1971 (Box-folder 6/14)
      - Releases and Employment Articles, 1975 (Box-folder 6/15)
      - Releases and Employment Articles, 1975 (Box-folder 6/16)
      - Press Statements and Releases, 1973-1981 (Box-folder 6/17)
      - Support Statements, 1972 (Box-folder 6/18)
    - Proposals, 1973-1976; Part 13 (Box-folder 6/19)
      - Miscellaneous, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 6/19)
    - Surveys, 1976-1977; Part 14 (Box-folder 6/20)
      - Surveys, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 6/20)
    - Discrimination Complaints, 1971-1975; Part 15 (Box-folder 6/21-6/22)
      - Discrimination Complaints, 1975 (Box-folder 6/21)
      - Discrimination Complaints, 1971 (Box-folder 6/22)
    - Fliers and Brochures, 1965-1985; Part 16 (Box-folder 6/23-6/25)
      - Fliers, leaflets and brochures, 1975 (Box-folder 6/23)
      - Brochure for UCWA, circa 1970s (Box-folder 6/24)
      - Fliers, leaflets and articles, 1976 (Box-folder 6/25)
    - Subject Series, 1962-1985; Part 17 (Box-folder 6/26-9/20)
      - Affirmative Action Plans, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 6/26)
      - Affirmative Action Plans (Ass't), 1970-1971 (Box-folder 6/27)
      - Affirmative Action, 1973 (Box-folder 6/28)
      - Affirmative Action, Equal Employment Opportunity, 1972 (Box-folder 6/29)
      - Asbestos, circa 1970s (Box-folder 6/30)
      - Attica/John Hill, 1975 (Box-folder 6/31)
      - Board of Public Works Contracts, 1971 (Box-folder 6/32)
      - Brownie's Art and Printing, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 6/33)
      - Carpenters, circa 1970s (Box-folder 6/34)
      - Seattle Central Community Council, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 6/35)
      - Central Contractors Association, 1971 (Box-folder 6/36)
      - El Centro de la Raza, 1972 (Box-folder 6/37)
      - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act Correspondence, 1979 (Box-folder 6/38)
      - Allen Jerome and Local 104 Lathers, 1975 (Box-folder 6/39)
      - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act Correspondence, 1978 (Box-folder 6/40)
      - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act Proposal and Employment Agreement, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 6/41)
      - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act Forms, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 6/42)
      - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act Correspondence, 1977 (Box-folder 6/43)
      - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 6/44)
      - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act Correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 6/45)
      - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act Correspondence, 1976 (Box-folder 6/46)
      - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act Title VI-A Desk Manual, 1979 (Box-folder 6/47)
      - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act, 1979 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act, 1979 (Box-folder 7/2)
      - Tyree's Trip to China, 1975 (Box-folder 7/3)
      - Community Meeting, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 7/4)
      - Community Service, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 7/5)
      - Compliance Officers, 1970 (Box-folder 7/6)
      - Construction Trade Information, 1971 (Box-folder 7/7)
      - Contract Compliance, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 7/8)
      - CONTROL (CONTRactors Organized to Lobby), 1970 (Box-folder 7/9)
      - Credit Union, circa 1970s (Box-folder 7/10)
      - Denver, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 7/11)
      - Denver's File, 1973 (Box-folder 7/12)
      - Trade Union Conference Denver, 1978 (Box-folder 7/13)
      - Employment Opportunities Center, 1973 (Box-folder 7/14)
      - Employment Discrimination, 1971 (Box-folder 7/15)
      - Equipment Operators (Local 302), 1970 (Box-folder 7/16)
      - Fundraising Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 7/17)
      - Fundraising Proposals, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 7/18)
      - Funding American Friends Service Committee, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 7/19)
      - Funding Proposal, circa 1970s (Box-folder 7/20)
      - Fundraising, Fall, 1974 (Box-folder 7/21)
      - Fundraising, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 7/22)
      - Fundraising -- Campaign for Human Development and Community Action and Human Development, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 7/23)
      - Campaign for Human Development (Part 1 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box-folder 7/24)
      - Campaign for Human Development (Part 2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box-folder 7/25)
      - Humanities Grants, 1978 (Box-folder 7/26)
      - Dan Hurvitz's Paper, circa 1970s (Box-folder 7/27)
      - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 46, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 7/28)
      - International Women's Day, 1978 (Box-folder 7/29)
      - International Women's Day Program, 1979 (Box-folder 7/30)
      - Juneteenth, 1979 (Box-folder 7/31)
      - Juneteenth, Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box-folder 7/32)
      - Joint Labor Negotiating Committee, 1980 (Box-folder 7/33)
      - KDP (Union of Democratic Filipinos), 1974 (Box-folder 7/34)
      - King-Snohomish Manpower Consortium, 1976 (Box-folder 7/35)
      - Ken A. Kirkpatrick, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 7/36)
      - Labor Laws, circa 1970s (Box-folder 7/37)
      - Lawyers Committee for Civil Rights, 1970 (Box-folder 7/38)
      - Light Brigade, 1977 (Box-folder 7/39)
      - Longshoremen, 1977 (Box-folder 7/40)
      - Machinist Training, 1974 (Box-folder 7/41)
      - Metal Trade (Washington), 1977 (Box-folder 7/42)
      - McKenzie River Gathering, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 7/43)
      - Midwest Academy, Michael Woo, 1974 (Box-folder 7/44)
      - Midwest Academy, 1975 (Box-folder 7/45)
      - Mozambique-- Film and Slide Show Presentation, 1978 (Box-folder 7/46)
      - National Association Minority Contractors, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 7/47)
      - National Conference of Christ and Jews, 1972 (Box-folder 7/48)
      - National Association Minority Contractors, 1970 (Box-folder 7/49)
      - No Separate Peace, 1976 (Box-folder 7/50)
      - No Separate Peace, 1975 (Box-folder 7/51)
      - No Separate Peace Meetings, 1976 (Box-folder 7/52)
      - No Separate Peace Meetings, 1976 (Box-folder 7/53)
      - No Separate Peace, 1976 (Box-folder 7/54)
      - No Separate Peace, February 1976 (Box-folder 7/55)
      - No Separate Peace Board Meeting, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 7/56)
      - No Separate Peace Newspapers, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 7/57)
      - No Separate Peace, 1976 (Box-folder 7/58)
      - No Separate Peace Drafts, 1976 (Box-folder 8/1)
      - No Separate Peace Drafts, 1975 (Box-folder 8/2)
      - No Separate Peace, 1975 (Box-folder 8/3)
      - No Separate Peace, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 8/4)
      - No Separate Peace Subscriptions, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 8/5)
      - No Separate Peace Evaluations, 1978 (Box-folder 8/6)
      - No Separate Peace, 1978 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - No Separate Peace, 1978 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - No Separate Peace, Photographs and Images for Publications, circa 1970s (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Oakland-Seattle Joint Meetings, 1973 (Box-folder 8/10)
      - Operation Breakthrough, 1972 (Box-folder 8/11)
      - Pack Rats Association, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 8/12)
      - Pan American World Airways, 1971 (Box-folder 8/13)
      - Parole and Work Release, 1971 (Box-folder 8/14)
      - Peace Task Force, 1972 (Box-folder 8/15)
      - Open House Originals- letters, surveys, and invitations, 1977 (Box-folder 8/16)
      - Picnic, 1977 (Box-folder 8/17)
      - Picnic, 1978 (Box-folder 8/18)
      - Picnic, 1975 (Box-folder 8/19)
      - Picnic Funds, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 8/20)
      - Picnic Committee, letters to send out, follow up material, 1973 (Box-folder 8/21)
      - Picnic Committee, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 8/22)
      - Pierce County Statistics, 1973 (Box-folder 8/23)
      - Poetry, 1975 (Box-folder 8/24)
      - Pittsburg Plan, 1970 (Box-folder 8/25)
      - Plumbers Strike Local 32, 1976 (Box-folder 8/26)
      - Port of Seattle, 1971 (Box-folder 8/27)
      - Port of Seattle, 1971 (Box-folder 8/28)
      - Portland, 1971 (Box-folder 8/29)
      - Programs, 1977 (Box-folder 8/30)
      - Project Equality, circa 1970s (Box-folder 8/31)
      - United Voice, Protests and Actions, 1971 (Box-folder 8/32)
      - Related Programs, 1970 (Box-folder 8/33)
      - San Francisco, 1972 (Box-folder 8/34)
      - San Francisco Operation Outreach, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 8/35)
      - City of Seattle, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 8/36)
      - Seattle Housing Authority, 1972 (Box-folder 8/37)
      - Seattle Model City Program, 1973 (Box-folder 8/38)
      - Model Cities Employment Survey, 1971 (Box-folder 8/39)
      - Seattle King County Plan, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 8/40)
      - Model Cities Related Materials, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 8/41)
      - Port of Seattle, 1977 (Box-folder 8/42)
      - Seattle City Council Committee, 1972 (Box-folder 8/43)
      - City Light, 1962-1974 (Box-folder 8/44)
      - Seattle/Opportunities Industrialization Center, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 8/45)
      - Seattle King-County Youth Action Council Summer Program, 1974 (Box-folder 8/46)
      - Sports Program, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 8/47)
      - Tacoma, City Government, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 8/48)
      - Teamsters, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 8/49)
      - Film Information, Third World Newsreel, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 8/50)
      - Third World Women's Task Force, 1978 (Box-folder 8/51)
      - Trade Library, 1971 (Box-folder 8/52)
      - Union Material, 1974 (Box-folder 8/53)
      - UAW Local 813, Unity Locals, 1977 (Box-folder 9/1)
      - Commission on Religion and Race of the United Methodist Church, 1971 (Box-folder 9/2)
      - Methodists, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 9/3)
      - Commission on Religion and Race of the United Methodist Church, 1973 (Box-folder 9/4)
      - United Minority Transport Workers Association, 1974 (Box-folder 9/5)
      - United Minority Workers By-Laws, circa 1970s (Box-folder 9/6)
      - Portland Proposal, United Minority Workers, 1973 (Box-folder 9/7)
      - Department of Justice, 1970 (Box-folder 9/8)
      - Department of Labor, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Proposed Rule-Making, 1971 (Box-folder 9/10)
      - U.S. Department of Labor Contract Efforts, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 9/11)
      - Equal Employment Opportunity, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 9/12)
      - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 9/13)
      - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission Title Seven Community Organizer, circa 1970s (Box-folder 9/14)
      - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission Contract and Other Material, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 9/15)
      - Post Office Information, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 9/16)
      - Wages - Minimum for Construction set by Federal Government, 1974 (Box-folder 9/17)
      - Washington State Manpower Planning Council, 1972 (Box-folder 9/18)
      - Washington State Manpower Planning Council, 1973 (Box-folder 9/19)
      - Women in Construction, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 9/20)
    - Register Attendance, 1965-1985; Part 18 (Box-folder 9/21-9/23)
      - Sign-In Register Book, circa 1970s (Box-folder 9/21)
      - Attendance Sheets, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 9/22)
      - Membership Mt. Attendance, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 9/23)
    - Lists, 1970-1978; Part 19 (Box-folder 9/24-9/25)
      - Lists, 1978 (Box-folder 9/24)
      - Workers and letters sent to them by us, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 9/25)
    - Notes, 1965-1985; Part 20 (Box-folder 9/26-9/28)
      - Notes from Beverly, 1978 (Box-folder 9/26)
      - Notes, 1972 (Box-folder 9/27)
      - Notes, circa 1970s (Box-folder 9/28)
    - Research Materials, 1965-1985; Part 21 (Box-folder 9/29-9/34)
      - Equal Employment Opportunity and Affirmative Action, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 9/29)
      - Research Materials, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 9/30)
      - Research Materials, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 9/31)
      - Research Materials, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 9/32)
      - "The Excepted People: The Migrant Workers in Washington State", circa 1970s (Box-folder 9/33)
      - Research Materials, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 9/34)
    - Forms, 1965-1985; Part 22 (Box-folder 9/35-10/3)
      - Membership Forms (Attendance, etc), circa 1970s (Box-folder 9/35)
      - Office Forms, circa 1970s (Box-folder 10/1)
      - Student worker applications, evaluations, circa 1970s (Box-folder 10/2)
      - Grievance Information, Discrimination charge, circa 1970s (Box-folder 10/3)
    - Ephemera, 1976-1978; Part 23 (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Ephemera, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 10/4)
    - Clippings, 1965-1985; Part 24 (Box-folder 10/5-10/10)
      - Miscellaneous Newspapers, Clippings and Articles, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 10/5)
      - Press Coverage, 1970 (Box-folder 10/6)
      - Miscellaneous Newspapers Articles, 1974 (Box-folder 10/7)
      - Clippings, 1973 (Box-folder 10/8)
      - Clippings, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 10/9)
      - Clippings from Scrapbooks, circa 1970s (Box-folder 10/10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965-1985; Part 25 (Box-folder 10/11-10/15)
      - Miscellaneous, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 10/11)
      - Certificates, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 10/12)
      - Daily Time Sheets, 1978 (Box-folder 10/13)
      - Songs, circa 1970s (Box-folder 10/14)
      - Correspondence and Publications, 1978 (Box-folder 10/15)
  - Board of Directors Records, 1965-1985; Subseries B (Box-folder 10/16-10/27)
    - Organizational Features, 1965-1985; Part 1 (Box-folder 10/16-10/18)
      - Rules of Order, circa 1970s (Box-folder 10/16)
      - Duties of the Board, circa 1970s (Box-folder 10/17)
      - UCWA Staff, 1976 (Box-folder 10/18)
    - Minutes and Agendas, 1971-1978; Part 2 (Box-folder 10/19-10/27)
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 1971 (Box-folder 10/19)
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 10/20)
      - Board Meeting Minutes and Notices, 1975 (Box-folder 10/21)
      - Board Meeting Minutes and Notices, 1976 (Box-folder 10/22)
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 10/23)
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 10/24)
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 10/25)
      - Board Meeting Agenda Items, 1977 (Box-folder 10/26)
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 10/27)
  - Electricians Committee, 1965-1985; Subseries C (Box-folder 10/28-11/8)
    - General Correspondence, 1971-1976; Part 1 (Box-folder 10/28-10/34)
      - Correspondence to Justice Department, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 10/28)
      - Letters to I.B.E.W. Local 46-ED or Hank, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 10/29)
      - All Other Correspondence to Committee, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 10/30)
      - Electricians Correspondence, 1974 (Box-folder 10/31)
      - Outgoing, 1976 (Box-folder 10/32)
      - Local 46 Memos to Sub-Committee, 1976 (Box-folder 10/33)
      - Outgoing Correspondence and Meeting Materials, 1976 (Box-folder 10/34)
    - Minutes, 1971-1978; Part 2 (Box-folder 10/35-10/39)
      - Minutes, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 10/35)
      - Minutes, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 10/36)
      - Minutes, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 10/37)
      - Sub-Committee Minutes and Correspondence, 1977 (Box-folder 10/38)
      - Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 10/39)
    - Education and Examinations, 1965-1985; Part 3 (Box-folder 10/40-11/1)
      - Journeyman Wireman Examination, 1972 (Box-folder 10/40)
      - Old Exams, circa 1970s (Box-folder 10/41)
      - Information, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 10/42)
      - Education and Examinations, circa 1970s (Box-folder 10/43)
      - Education and Examinations (1 of 2), circa 1970s (Box-folder 10/44)
      - Education and Examinations (2 of 2), circa 1970s (Box-folder 10/45)
      - Education and Examinations, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 11/1)
    - Attendance Records, 1975-1976; Part 4 (Box-folder 11/2-11/3)
      - Electricians Classes, 1975 (Box-folder 11/2)
      - Electricians Attendance Sheets/Materials, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 11/3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974-1976; Part 5 (Box-folder 11/4-11/6)
      - Apprenticeship Standards, 1974 (Box-folder 11/4)
      - Miscellaneous, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 11/5)
      - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box-folder 11/6)
    - Special Apprenticeship Sub-Committee, 1972-1974; Part 6 (Box-folder 11/7-11/8)
      - Special Apprenticeship Sub-Committee, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 11/7)
      - Special Electrical Apprenticeship Sub-Committee, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 11/8)
  - Ironworkers Committee, 1971-1976; Subseries D (Box-folder 11/9-11/11)
    - Ironworkers Committee, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 11/9)
    - Attendance Sheets/Materials, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 11/10)
    - Ironworkers Committee, 1976 (Box-folder 11/11)
  - Oilers and Operators Committee, 1970-1977; Subseries E (Box-folder 11/12-11/18)
    - Operating Engineers Attendance Sheets/Materials, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 11/12)
    - Oilers and Operators Committee, 1976 (Box-folder 11/13)
    - Operating Engineers Joint Apprenticeship Committee (JATC) Minutes, 1976 (Box-folder 11/14)
    - Oilers and Operators Committee, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 11/15)
    - Oilers and Operators Committee, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 11/16)
    - Operating Engineers, 1972 (Box-folder 11/17)
    - Operating Engineers, 1977 (Box-folder 11/18)
  - Plumbers and Pipefitters Committee, 1965-1978; Subseries F (Box-folder 11/19-11/22)
    - Meeting Materials, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 11/19)
    - Plumbers and Pipefitters Committee, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 11/20)
    - Mailing Lists and Applications, circa 1970s (Box-folder 11/21)
    - Plumbers and Pipefitters Committee, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 11/22)
  - Sheetmetal Workers Committee, 1970-1976; Subseries G (Box-folder 11/23-11/27)
    - Sheetmetal Workers Awaiting Jobs, 1970 (Box-folder 11/23)
    - Sheetmetal Workers Committee, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 11/24)
    - Sheetmetal Workers Committee, 1975 (Box-folder 11/25)
    - Sheetmetal Workers Recommendations, 1976 (Box-folder 11/26)
    - Sheetmetal Workers Attendance Sheets/Materials, 1976 (Box-folder 11/27)
  - Oakland Board of Directors, 1965-1985; Subseries H (Box-folder 11/28-)
    - Seattle and Oakland Board of Directors Correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder 11/28)
    - Seattle and Oakland Board of Directors Meeting Agendas and Attendance, 1973 (Box-folder 11/29)
    - Oakland Board of Directors Agenda, circa 1970s (Box-folder 11/30)
    - Seattle and Oakland Inhouse Correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder 11/31)
    - Oakland Financial Statements, February 1974-July 1974 (Box-folder 11/32)
    - Oakland Board of Directors Minutes, 1973 (Box-folder 11/33)
- COURT ORDER ADVISORY COMMITTEE RECORDS, 1965-1985; SERIES 2 (Box-folder 11/34-12/16)
  - Historical and Organizational Features, 1965-1985; Subseries A (Box-folder 11/34-11/35)
    - By-Laws, circa 1970s (Box-folder 11/34)
    - Historical and Organizational Features, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 11/35)
  - Incoming Letters, 1970-1979; Subseries B (Box-folder 11/36-11/39-)
    - Lindberg, William J., Judge, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 11/36)
    - Seattle Area Plumbing and Pipefitting Apprenticeship and Journeyman Training Trust, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 11/37)
    - Incoming Letters, United Construction Workers Association, 1976 (Box-folder 11/38)